Guide to the National Education Association-Conventions records, 1857-1998 NEA1008.RG
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Conventions and Conferences, Bulk, 1970-1996 1858-1998; 1970-1996; Series 1; National Education Association of the United States. Meeting.; 85 Linear Feet
  - Conventions-News Coverage [file 1/2], 1978; Series 1 (Box 1497, Folder 5)
  - Conventions-News Coverage [file 2/2], 1978; Series 1 (Box 1497, Folder 6)
  - Conventions-News Coverage, 1979; Series 1 (Box 1497, Folder 7)
  - Conventions-News Coverage, 1980; Series 1 (Box 1497, Folder 8)
  - Conventions-News Coverage, 1981; Series 1 (Box 1498, Folder 1)
  - Conventions-News Coverage, 1982; Series 1 (Box 1498, Folder 2)
  - Conventions-News Coverage, 1983; Series 1 (Box 1498, Folder 3)
  - Conventions-Newspaper Clippings (Minneapolis, MN), 1928; Series 1 (Box 1498, Folder 4)
  - Conventions-"Official Manual for Delegates", June 1923; Series 1 (Box 1498, Folder 5)
  - Conventions-Omissions from the Volumes of Proceedings, circa 1890; Series 1 (Box 1498, Folder 6)
  - Conventions-"An Open Letter to America on Schools, Students and Tomorrow", circa 1995; Series 1 (Box 1498, Folder 7)
  - Conventions-"Operation Rescue", 1985; Series 1 (Box 1498, Folder 8)
  - Conventions-Papers and Addresses Delivered at the General Sessions of the World's Educational Congresses, 1893; Series 1 (Box 1498, Folder 9)
  - Conventions-Photos, 1973; Series 1 (Box 1498, Folder 10)
    Contains 6 photos.
  - Conventions-Photos, 1974; Series 1 (Box 1498, Folder 11)
    Contains 8 photos.
  - Conventions-Placement Service, 1965; Series 1 (Box 1498, Folder 12)
  - Conventions-Press Release (Los Angeles, CA), 1975; Series 1 (Box 1498, Folder 13)
  - Conventions-Press Releases, 1985-1986; Series 1 (Box 1499, Folder 1)
  - Convention Programs [1/7], 1890-1975; Series 1 (Box 3319, Folder 1)
  - Convention Programs [2/7], 1890-1975; Series 1 (Box 3319, Folder 2)
  - Convention Programs [3/7], 1890-1975; Series 1 (Box 3319, Folder 3)
  - Convention Programs [4/7], 1890-1975; Series 1 (Box 3319, Folder 4)
  - Convention Programs [5/7], 1890-1975; Series 1 (Box 3320, Folder 1)
  - Convention Programs [6/7], 1890-1975; Series 1 (Box 3320, Folder 2)
  - Convention Programs [7/7], 1890-1975; Series 1 (Box 3320, Folder 3)
  - Convention Programs, 1869-1899; Series 1 (Box 3958, Folder 1)
  - Convention Programs, 1900-1908; Series 1 (Box 3958, Folder 2)
  - Convention Programs, 1909-1912; Series 1 (Box 3958, Folder 3)
  - Convention Programs, 1913-1916; Series 1 (Box 3958, Folder 4)
  - Convention Programs, 1917-1921; Series 1 (Box 3958, Folder 5)
  - Convention Programs, 1922-1925; Series 1 (Box 3958, Folder 6)
  - Convention Programs, 1926-1929; Series 1 (Box 3959, Folder 1)
  - Convention Programs, 1930-1932; Series 1 (Box 3959, Folder 2)
  - Convention Programs, 1933-1936; Series 1 (Box 3959, Folder 3)
  - Convention Programs, 1937-1939; Series 1 (Box 3959, Folder 4)
  - Convention Programs, 1940-1942; Series 1 (Box 3959, Folder 5)
  - Convention Programs, Buttons, Postcards, and Ribbons, 1888-1903, 1956; Series 1 (Box 4040, Folder 16)
  - Conventions-Publishers of the Proceedings, 1966; Series 1 (Box 1499, Folder 2)
  - Conventions-"Reports", 1908; Series 1 (Box 1499, Folder 3)
  - Conventions-Reports-"1969 Convention Report", Series 1 (Box 1499, Folder 4)
  - Conventions-Reports-"1969-1970 Annual Report", circa 1970; Series 1 (Box 1499, Folder 5)
    Contains a decal and a 33 1/3 RPM plastic record entitled, "My Term as President, George D. Fischer, July 1, 1970".
  - Conventions-Reports-"Educational Actions", 1974; Series 1 (Box 1499, Folder 6)
  - Conventions-Reports-"Educational Actions", 1975; Series 1 (Box 1499, Folder 7)
  - Conventions-Reports-"Educational Actions", 1976; Series 1 (Box 1499, Folder 8)
  - Conventions-Reports-"Educational Actions", 1978; Series 1 (Box 1499, Folder 9)
  - Conventions-Reports-"Educational Actions", 1979; Series 1 (Box 1499, Folder 10)
  - Conventions-Reports-"Legislation", 1980; Series 1 (Box 1499, Folder 11)
  - Conventions-Reports-"NEA's Financial Future-1975 and Beyond", Series 1 (Box 1499, Folder 12)
  - Conventions-Reports-"Presenting the Votomatic", 1975; Series 1 (Box 1499, Folder 13)
  - Conventions-Reports-"Program Budget, Fiscal Year 1980-1981", Series 1 (Box 1499, Folder 14)
  - Conventions-Reports-"Report on the Annual Meeting of the National Education Association", 1981; Series 1 (Box 1500, Folder 1)
  - Conventions-Reports-"Reports on Implementation of Actions of the 1974 Representative Assembly", 1975; Series 1 (Box 1500, Folder 2)
  - Conventions-Reports-"Reports on Implementation of Actions of the 1979 Representative Assembly", 1980; Series 1 (Box 1500, Folder 3)
  - Conventions-Reports-"Reports on Implementation of Actions of the 1980 Representative Assembly", 1981; Series 1 (Box 1500, Folder 4)
  - Conventions-Reports-"Reports on Implementation of Actions of the 1981 Representative Assembly", 1982; Series 1 (Box 1500, Folder 5)
  - Conventions-Reports-"Reports on Implementation of Actions of the 1982 Representative Assembly", 1983; Series 1 (Box 1500, Folder 6)
  - Conventions-Reports-"Teacher Unity-Year One", 1974; Series 1 (Box 1500, Folder 7)
  - Conventions-Reports-"What Price Quotas?", circa 1972; Series 1 (Box 1500, Folder 8)
  - Conventions-"Representative Assembly Communique", 1977-1983; Series 1 (Box 1500, Folder 9)
  - Conventions-"Representative Assembly Communique", 1985; Series 1 (Box 1500, Folder 10)
  - Conventions-Requirements for the Allocation and Election of Delegates to the NEA Representative Assembly, 1976-1981; Series 1 (Box 1500, Folder 11)
  - Conventions-Revision Study, 1957-1965; Series 1 (Box 1500, Folder 12)
  - Conventions-Revision Study, 1962; Series 1 (Box 1500, Folder 13)
  - Conventions-Revision Study, 1966; Series 1 (Box 1500, Folder 14)
  - Conventions-"School and Society", July 1934; Series 1 (Box 1500, Folder 15)
  - Conventions-Scrapbook (1960 Convention), Series 1 (Box 1501, Oversize 1)
  - Conventions-Selected Copies of Proceedings (Xeroxes), 1858-1869; Series 1 (Box 1500, Folder 16)
  - Conventions-Site Selection, 1971-1972; Series 1 (Box 1500, Folder 17)
  - Conventions-Speeches/Statements, 1985-1986; Series 1 (Box 1502, Folder 1)
  - Conventions-Transcript [file 1/3], July 1962; Series 1 (Box 1502, Folder 2)
  - Conventions-Transcript [file 2/3], July 1962; Series 1 (Box 1502, Folder 3)
  - Conventions-Transcript [file 3/3], July 1962; Series 1 (Box 1502, Folder 4)
  - Conventions-"What to Look for When you Visit your Child's School", June 1985; Series 1 (Box 1502, Folder 5)
  - Conventions-"The Year of the Teacher", 1985; Series 1 (Box 1502, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, 1989-1990; Series 1 (Box 1502, Folder 7)
  - [Correspondence Regarding the 2003 NEA Northeast Regional Leadership Conference], 2002 October- 2002 December; Series 1 (Box 4657, Folder 7)
  - Critical Issues Conference (1975), July 1975; Series 1 (Box 1502, Folder 8)
  - The Critical Issues Conference Programs, 1974, 1983; series 1 (Box 4418, Folder 25)
  - Data Processing Meeting (1989) [file 1/2], 1987-1988; Series 1 (Box 1503, Folder 1)
  - Data Processing Meeting (1989) [file 2/2], 1987-1988; Series 1 (Box 1503, Folder 2)
  - Data Processing Meeting (1990) [file 1/3], 1988-1990; Series 1 (Box 1503, Folder 3)
  - Data Processing Meeting (1990) [file 2/3], 1988-1990; Series 1 (Box 1503, Folder 4)
  - Data Processing Meeting (1990) [file 3/3], 1988-1990; Series 1 (Box 1503, Folder 5)
  - Data Processing Meeting (1991) [file 1/2], 1989; Series 1 (Box 1504, Folder 1)
  - Data Processing Meeting (1991) [file 2/2], 1989; Series 1 (Box 1504, Folder 2)
  - Data Processing User Meeting, 1990-1992; Series 1 (Box 1504, Folder 3)
  - Data Processing Workshop, 1987-1988; Series 1 (Box 1504, Folder 4)
  - Delegates Manual and Program, 1947-07-07-1947-07-11; Series 1 (Box 4933, Folder 2)
  - DELETE, July 1-6, 1997; Series 1 (Box 4632, Folder 9)
  - Donna Ullman's Cluster Training Meeting (1990) [file 1/2], 1989; Series 1 (Box 1505, Folder 1)
  - Donna Ullman's Cluster Training Meeting (1990) [file 2/2], 1989; Series 1 (Box 1505, Folder 2)
  - Donna Ullman's Cluster Training Meetings [file 1/2], 1989-1991; Series 1 (Box 1505, Folder 3)
  - Donna Ullman's Cluster Training Meetings [file 2/2], 1989-1991; Series 1 (Box 1505, Folder 4)
  - Ed/EX '72 the New Things, June 1972; series 1 (Box 4418, Folder 26)
  - Educational Excellence and Access for Every Student NEA Joint Conference on Concerns of Minorities and Women, June 1987; series 1 (Box 4418, Folder 27)
  - Evaluation Results, 2003 January 24-26; Series 1 (Box 4657, Folder 8)
  - Excellence in Instruction: Report of the 11th Regional Conference on Instruction, November 23-25, 1961; Series 1 (Box 4057, Folder 7)
  - Excerpt of Minutes of Philidelphia Convention, 1926; series 1 (Box 4418, Folder 28)
  - Executive Committee Retreat (1988) [file 1/2], Series 1 (Box 1505, Folder 5)
  - Executive Committee Retreat (1988) [file 2/2], Series 1 (Box 1506, Folder 1)
  - Executive Staff Meeting (1990), Series 1 (Box 1506, Folder 2)
  - Exhibit at the 1971 Convention, June 1971; series 1 (Box 4418, Folder 29)
  - Fifteenth National Conference on School Finance, 1972; series 1 (Box 4418, Folder 30)
  - Financial Reports: Secretary-Treasurer Independent Auditors, 2000 July; Series 1 (Box 4988, Folder 3)
  - Funded Participants, Northeast Regional Leadership Conference-Atlantic City, New Jersey, 2005 January 28-30; Series 1 (Box 4657, Folder 9)
  - Guide to the 1987 NEA Annual Meeting, series 1 (Box 4418, Folder 31)
  - Guide to the 1992 National education Association Annual Meeting, 1992 July 3 - 8; Series 1 (Box 4971, Folder 8)
  - Highlights of the 1965 White House Conference on Education, series 1 (Box 4381, Folder 22)
  - Hotel Bill, NEA Northeast Regional Leadership Conference, 2003; Series 1 (Box 4657, Folder 10)
  - The International Conference on Education, 1877; series 1 (Box 4310, Folder 14)
  - IPD State Staffs Meeting, 1988; Series 1 (Box 1506, Folder 3)
  - Justice For All Meeting (1990), Series 1 (Box 1506, Folder 4)
  - [Loose in Box], 1988-2002; Series 1 (Box 4781, Folder 16)
  - LSP Meeting, 1990; Series 1 (Box 1506, Folder 5)
  - Marriott Group Sales Agreement, 2002; Series 1 (Box 4657, Folder 11)
  - Mastery on Learning, 1990; Series 1 (Box 1506, Folder 6)
  - Meeting Standards, 1989; Series 1 (Box 1506, Folder 7)
  - Metropolitan Transportation Services Inc. (MTSI), 1989-1990; Series 1 (Box 1506, Folder 8)
  - Miami Site Inspection File [file 1/2], 1988; Series 1 (Box 1506, Folder 9)
  - Miami Site Inspection File [file 2/2], 1988; Series 1 (Box 1506, Folder 10)
  - Mid-Atlantic Regional Leadership Conference, 1990; Series 1 (Box 1506, Folder 11)
  - Mid-Atlantic Regional Leadership Conference (1988), 1987-1988; Series 1 (Box 1506, Folder 12)
  - Minority Teacher Shortage Meeting (1990), Series 1 (Box 1506, Folder 13)
  - Mystic Marriott Hotel Master Summary, 2004; Series 1 (Box 4657, Folder 12)
  - Mystic Marriott Hotel and Spa Menus, Undated; Series 1 (Box 4658, Folder 1)
  - National Center for the Study of Collective Bargaining in Higher Education/Proceedings Second Annual Conference/Collective Bargaining in Higher Education, 1974 April; Series 1 (Box 4998, Folder 8)
  - National Center for the Study of Collective Bargaining in Higher Education/Proceedings Third Annual Conference/Collective Bargaining in Higher Education, 1975 April; Series 1 (Box 4998, Folder 9)
  - National Center for the Study of Collective Bargaining in Higher Education/Proceedings Fourth Annual Conference/Collective Bargaining in Higher Education, 1976 April; Series 1 (Box 4998, Folder 10)
  - National Center for the Study of Collective Bargaining in Higher Education/Proceedings Fifth Annual Conference/Collective Bargaining and the Future of Higher Education, 1977 April; Series 1 (Box 4999, Folder 1)
  - National Center for the Study of Collective Bargaining in Higher Education/Proceedings Sixth Annual Conference/The Uniqueness of Collective Bargaining in Higher Education, 1978 April; Series 1 (Box 4999, Folder 2)
  - National Center for the Study of Collective Bargaining in Higher Education/Proceedings Seventh Annual Conference/Landmarks in Collective Bargaining in Higher Education, 1979 April; Series 1 (Box 4998, Folder 7)
  - National Center for the Study of Collective Bargaining in Higher Education/Proceedings Eighth Annual Conference, 1980 April; Series 1 (Box 4999, Folder 3)
  - National Center for the Study of Collective Bargaining in Higher Education and the Professions/Proceedings Tenth Annual Conference/Campus Bargaining at the Crossroads, 1982 April; Series 1 (Box 4999, Folder 4)
  - National Center for the Study of Collective Bargaining in Higher Education and the Professions/Proceedings Eleventh Annual Conference/Collective Bargaining in a Period of Retrenchment, 1983 April; Series 1 (Box 4999, Folder 5)
  - National Center for the Study of Collective Bargaining in Higher Education and the Professions/Proceedings Fourteenth Annual Conference/The Unionized Professoriate: A Discriminating Appraisal, 1986 April; Series 1 (Box 4999, Folder 6)
  - National Center for the Study of Collective Bargaining in Higher Education and the Professions/Proceedings Sixteenth Annual Conference/Collective Bargaining and the Economic Condition of Higher Education, 1988 April; Series 1 (Box 4999, Folder 7)
  - National Center for the Study of Collective Bargaining in Higher Education and the Professions/Proceedings Eighteenth Annual Conference/Collective Bargaining in Higher Education: The 1990's, 1990 April; Series 1 (Box 4999, Folder 8)
  - National Center for the Study of Collective Bargaining in Higher Education and the Professions/Proceedings Nineteenth Annual Conference/Collective Bargaining in Higher Education: Leadership in Uncertain Times, 1991 March; Series 1 (Box 4999, Folder 9)
  - National Center for the Study of Collective Bargaining in Higher Education and the Professions/Proceedings Twentieth Annual Conference/The Impact of Collective Bargaining on Higher Education: A Twenty Year Retrospective, 1992 April; Series 1 (Box 4999, Folder 10)
  - National Center for the Study of Collective Bargaining in Higher Education and the Professions/Proceedings Twenty-First Annual Conference/Unions and Management: Working Our Way Out of Fiscal Stress, 1993 April; Series 1 (Box 5000, Folder 1)
  - National Center for the Study of Collective Bargaining in Higher Education and the Professions/Proceedings Twenty-Third Annual Conference/Higher Education Collective Bargaining: Beyond the Boundaries, 1995 April; Series 1 (Box 5000, Folder 2)
  - National Center for the Study of Collective Bargaining in Higher Education and the Professions/Proceedings Twenty-Fourth Annual Conference/Higher Education Collective Bargaining: Back to "CB" Basics, 1996 April; Series 1 (Box 5000, Folder 3)
  - National Center for the Study of Collective Bargaining in Higher Education and the Professions/Proceedings Twenty-Sixth Annual Conference/Responding to Challenges and Conflict in Higher Education Collective Bargaining, 1998 April; Series 1 (Box 5000, Folder 4)
  - National Center for the Study of Collective Bargaining in Higher Education and the Professions/Proceedings Twenty-Seventh Annual Conference/Collective Bargaining and Accountability in Higher Education: A Report Card, 1999 April; Series 1 (Box 5000, Folder 5)
  - National Conference on Single Parent Families and the Schools, March 1983; series 1 (Box 4351, Folder 23)
  - National Organization of Lawyers for Education Associations (1989) [file 1/3], 1987-1989; Series 1 (Box 1507, Folder 1)
  - National Organization of Lawyers for Education Associations (1989) [file 2/3], 1987-1989; Series 1 (Box 1507, Folder 2)
  - National Organization of Lawyers for Education Associations (1989) [file 3/3], 1987-1989; Series 1 (Box 1507, Folder 3)
  - NEA Mobilizes For Action Advancing The Nation's Education Agenda, Undated; Series (Box 4869, Folder 1)
  - NEA All Staff Meeting and Reception, September 13, 2011; Series 1 (Box 4803, Folder 7)
  - NEA Conference on Quality Schools and Adequate Learning, May 8-10, 2002; Series 1 (Box 4781, Folder 17)
  - NEA Flyers and Advertisements, 2000 July; Series 1 (Box 4988, Folder 4)
  - NEA News: NEA Delegates Tackle Tough Issues at 2005 Annual Meeting, Series 1 (Box 4708, Folder 16)
  - NEA Northeast Regional Leadership Conference- Angel Dorta Registration Form, 2004 October 18; Series 1 (Box 4658, Folder 2)
  - NEA Northeast Regional Leadership Conference-Boston Marriott-Copley Place, 2003 January 22-26; Series 1 (Box 4658, Folder 3)
  - NEA Northeast Regional Leadership Conference- Group Sales and Room Agreements, 2003; Series 1 (Box 4658, Folder 4)
  - [NEA Northeast Regional Leadership Conference Logistics], 2003; Series 1 (Box 4658, Folder 5)
  - [NEA Northeast Regional Leadership Conference Logistics and Hotel Banquet Event Order], 2004; Series 1 (Box 4658, Folder 6)
  - [NEA Northeast Regional Leadership Conference Materials], 2002; Series 1 (Box 4658, Folder 7)
  - NEA Northeast Regional Leadership Conference- Mystic, CT, 2003-2004; Series 1 (Box 4658, Folder 8)
  - NEA Northeast Regional Leadership Conference- Mystic, CT State Registration Forms, 2004; Series 1 (Box 4658, Folder 9)
  - NEA Northeast Regional Leadership Conference Pre-Planning Meeting- Mystic, CT, 2003; Series 1 (Box 4658, Folder 10)
  - NEA Northeast Regional Leadership Conference Registration Forms- Atlantic City, NJ, 2005 January 28-30; Series 1 (Box 4658, Folder 11)
  - NEA Northeast Regional Leadership Conference Registration Form Email Correspondence, 2004 November; Series 1 (Box 4658, Folder 12)
  - NEA Northeast Regional Leadership Conference Resolution Hearings- Mystic, CT, 2003; Series 1 (Box 4658, Folder 13)
  - NEA Northeast Regional Leadership Conference Workshop and Conference Evaluation Results, 2004 January; Series 1 (Box 4658, Folder 14)
  - NEA Organizing 2000, 1990; Series 1 (Box 1506, Folder 14)
  - "NEA Rates Phila. Good, but Not Great", July 1983; series 1 (Box 4420, Folder 5)
  - NEA State Leaders Conference, 2010 July 16-20; Series 1 (Box 5000, Folder 6)
  - NEASO Meeting, 1990; Series 1 (Box 1506, Folder 15)
  - Non-NEA Funded Participants- Atlantic City, NJ [1/2], 2005 January 28-30; Series 1 (Box 4659, Folder 1)
  - Non-NEA Funded Participants- Atlantic City, NJ [2/2], 2005 January 28-30; Series 1 (Box 4659, Folder 2)
  - Northeast Region Conference Planning Committee Meeting, 2003 May 1; Series 1 (Box 4659, Folder 3)
  - Northeast Regional Leadership Conference Planning Committee Meeting, 2003-2004; Series 1 (Box 4659, Folder 4)
  - Northeast Region Planning Committee Meeting, 2003 February 6; Series 1 (Box 4659, Folder 7)
  - Northeast Regional Leadership Conference Planning Committee Meeting- Mystic, CT, 2003 August 11-12; Series 1 (Box 4659, Folder 5)
  - Northeast Regional Leadership Conference Planning Committee Meeting- Washington, D.C., 2003 December 11; Series 1 (Box 4659, Folder 6)
  - NSAII-IPD, 1990; Series 1 (Box 1507, Folder 4)
  - [Packet for Delegates at Representative Assembly], 1999; Series 1 (Box 4659, Folder 8)
  - [Packet for Delegates at Representative Assembly], 2002; Series 1 (Box 4660, Folder 1)
  - [Packet for Delegates at Representative Assembly], 2004; Series 1 (Box 4660, Folder 2)
  - Pending Participation in Annual Conventions, 1989; Series 1 (Box 1507, Folder 5)
  - Professional Standards Clinic (1990), Series 1 (Box 1507, Folder 6)
  - Public Education Achieving America's Potential, Undated; Series (Box 4869, Folder 3)
  - Political Power Fro Educational Excellence, Undated; Series (Box 4869, Folder 2)
  - Press Report RA 2000 July 1, 2000 Chicago, IL, Series 1 (Box 4988, Folder 5)
  - Public Education is a Public Trust, Undated; Series (Box 4869, Folder 4)
  - Public Schools: Fulfilling the AMerican Dream- 131st Annual Meeting, June 30-July 5, 1993; Series 1 (Box 4706, Folder 1)
  - Quality Teaching for All Children Report: 8th Regional Conference on Instruction, April 10-13, 1960; Series 1 (Box 4057, Folder 8)
  - RA Today, 1996 July 6; Series 1 (Box 5015, Folder 1)
  - RA Today, 1997 July 1; Series 1 (Box 5015, Folder 2)
  - RA Today, 1997 July 2; Series 1 (Box 5015, Folder 3)
  - RA Today, 1997 July 3; Series 1 (Box 5015, Folder 4)
  - RA Today, 1997 July 4; Series 1 (Box 5015, Folder 5)
  - RA Today, 1997 July 5; Series 1 (Box 5015, Folder 6)
  - RA Today, 1997 July 6; Series 1 (Box 5015, Folder 7)
  - RA Today, 1997 July 7; Series 1 (Box 5015, Folder 8)
  - RA Today, 1998 July 1; Series 1 (Box 5015, Folder 9)
  - RA Today, 1998 July 2; Series 1 (Box 5015, Folder 10)
  - RA Today, 1998 July 3; Series 1 (Box 5015, Folder 11)
  - RA Today, 1998 July 4; Series 1 (Box 5015, Folder 12)
  - RA Today, 1998 July 5; Series 1 (Box 5016, Folder 1)
  - RA Today, 1998 July 6; Series 1 (Box 5016, Folder 2)
  - RA Today, 1999; Series 1 (Box 5016, Folder 3)
  - RA Today, 2000 July 1; Series 1 (Box 4988, Folder 6)
  - RA Today, 2000 July 2; Series 1 (Box 4988, Folder 7)
  - RA Today, July 3, 2004; Series 1 (Box 4950, Folder 1)
  - RA Today, July 4, 2004; Series 1 (Box 4950, Folder 2)
  - RA Today, July 5, 2004; Series 1 (Box 4950, Folder 3)
  - RA Today, July 6, 2004; Series 1 (Box 4950, Folder 4)
  - RA Today, July 7, 2004; Series 1 (Box 4950, Folder 5)
  - RA Today, July 8, 2004; Series 1 (Box 4950, Folder 6)
  - RA Today, 2005 July 2; Series 1 (Box 5016, Folder 4)
  - RA Today, July 2, 2005; Series 1 (Box 4950, Folder 7)
  - RA Today, 2005 July 3; Series 1 (Box 5016, Folder 5)
  - RA Today, July 3, 2005; Series 1 (Box 4950, Folder 8)
  - RA Today, 2005 July 4; Series 1 (Box 5016, Folder 6)
  - RA Today, July 4, 2005; Series 1 (Box 4950, Folder 9)
  - RA Today, 2005 July 5; Series 1 (Box 5016, Folder 7)
  - RA Today, July 5, 2005; Series 1 (Box 4950, Folder 10)
  - RA Today, 2005 July 6; Series 1 (Box 5016, Folder 8)
  - RA Today, July 6, 2005; Series 1 (Box 4950, Folder 11)
  - RA Today, 2005 July 7; Series 1 (Box 5016, Folder 9)
  - RA Today, July 7, 2005; Series 1 (Box 4950, Folder 12)
  - RA Today, 2005; Series 1 (Box 5016, Folder 10)
  - RA Today, 2006 July 1; Series 1 (Box 5016, Folder 11)
  - RA Today, 2006 July 2; Series 1 (Box 5016, Folder 12)
  - RA Today, 2006 July 3; Series 1 (Box 5017, Folder 1)
  - RA Today, 2006 July 4; Series 1 (Box 5017, Folder 2)
  - RA Today, 2006 July 5; Series 1 (Box 5017, Folder 3)
  - RA Today, 2006 July 6; Series 1 (Box 5017, Folder 4)
  - RA Today, 2006; Series 1 (Box 5017, Folder 5)
  - RA Today, 2007 July 1; Series 1 (Box 5017, Folder 6)
  - RA Today, 2007 July 2; Series 1 (Box 5035, Folder 6)
  - RA Today, 2007 July 2; Series 1 (Box 5017, Folder 7)
  - RA Today, 2007 July 3; Series 1 (Box 5017, Folder 8)
  - RA Today, 2007 July 4; Series 1 (Box 5017, Folder 9)
  - RA Today, 2007 July 5; Series 1 (Box 5017, Folder 10)
  - RA Today, 2007 July 6; Series 1 (Box 5017, Folder 11)
  - RA Today, 2007; Series 1 (Box 5017, Folder 12)
  - RA Today, 2008 July 2; Series 1 (Box 5018, Folder 1)
  - RA Today, 2008 July 3; Series 1 (Box 5018, Folder 2)
  - RA Today, 2008 July 4; Series 1 (Box 5018, Folder 3)
  - RA Today, 2008 July 5; Series 1 (Box 5018, Folder 4)
  - RA Today, 2008 July 6; Series 1 (Box 5018, Folder 5)
  - RA Today, 2008 July 7; Series 1 (Box 5018, Folder 6)
  - RA Today, 2009 July 2; Series 1 (Box 5018, Folder 7)
  - RA Today, 2009 July 3; Series 1 (Box 5018, Folder 8)
  - RA Today, 2009 July 4; Series 1 (Box 5018, Folder 9)
  - RA Today, 2009 July 5; Series 1 (Box 5018, Folder 10)
  - RA Today, 2009 July 6; Series 1 (Box 5018, Folder 11)
  - RA Today, 2009 July 7; Series 1 (Box 5018, Folder 12)
  - RA Today, 2010 July 2; Series 1 (Box 5019, Folder 1)
  - RA Today, 2010 July 3; Series 1 (Box 5019, Folder 2)